<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<feed xmlns="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><title>J U L I U S R E A D E</title><link href="/" rel="alternate"></link><link href="/feeds/coding.atom.xml" rel="self"></link><id>/</id><updated>2016-06-10T20:14:00+10:00</updated><entry><title>coding</title><link href="/coding/coding" rel="alternate"></link><published>2016-06-10T20:14:00+10:00</published><author><name>Julius Reade</name></author><id>tag:,2016-06-09:coding/coding</id><summary type="html">
	
</summary><category term="coding"></category></entry><entry><title>My coding article</title><link href="/coding/timtimtim" rel="alternate"></link><published>2010-12-05T19:30:00+11:00</published><author><name>Julius Reade</name></author><id>tag:,2010-12-03:coding/timtimtim</id><summary type="html">&lt;p&gt;I don’t get it. I mean, it’s like my head is raging, or something. In my skull is this brittle imagination that veers into dysfunction, as if designed to tear into my validity and grind against the clouding inertia. It holds me relentlessly, cradling me into a lull diaspora; a cultural reminder of my own fatal imperfection, tricking me into fashionable atrophy. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;I guess, figuratively speaking, if you were to quiet the mind and empty your thoughts, life may approach a sharp minimum. Instead of running circles around your squares, you may instead, develop a sense of concentration and even utilise your talents to enhance reality, rather than pick at the toxic scraps of shitty relationships and grand delusions littering your mind. I mean, no one wants to be dragged against the ground, kicking and screaming as your fate decides the cumbersome tatter to your path, but that’s just the soup of the day. Eat your bread and shut up.  &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;We all went through that period in life where we thought we were fantastic, like when we lost our shit crossing our eyes to produce two overlapping images, becoming gods within the midst. In that short moment of glamour, we felt smart, almost scandalous. We felt like a pulsing Hollywood, like some kind of Jimmy Neutron. Unfortunately, the good looks were just a ruse, and the taste... no one even cares. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;Thankfully, you don’t need to be special when you’re already human. It’s a fact that these hands can do just about anything your hands can do, and while my hands are likely more beautiful, well, there’s no overcoming facts. Listen, I apologise. It’s these sentimental aptitudes, so devoid of feeling and emotion, so inexperienced for it’s own sake, that you’d just crawl up into a ball and cry it out. Movies will do that to you, music too. &lt;/p&gt;
&lt;p&gt;“My brain simmers like a fried egg, extruding blue cheese onto a dollop of thick mayo, uncanny impairment trickling sour corporation. Savoury lemons, tarty goodness; lustful hand-processed kale, strung so thick around my tubes it suffocates the wobble pertaining my vague neurological paralysis. I’m starving.”
So here I am. A vulnerable, emotional wreck of a fried egg, saddled with guilt so deep it penetrates my consciousness and permeates into description of food, reminding me of my failure as a human being. If only I were a transgender jellyfish, floating with a kick of flirt. The good news is that I also highly motivated and effective human being, bent destroying the world with my ability to string words into sentences, because that’s just what my fingers do. I am not a right &lt;/p&gt;</summary><category term="coding"></category></entry></feed>